ROB DODSON: Hey there, folks, Rob here.
ROB DODSON：嘿，伙计们，Rob在这里。
Welcome back to the show.
欢迎回到表演。
So it's been a while since we did one of these,
自从我们做了其中一个以来已经有一段时间了，
but I thought today would be a good time
但我认为今天会是个好时机
to do another episode of Ask Polymer.
进行另一集的Ask Polymer。
So I went on Twitter, I asked folks
所以我去了Twitter，我问乡亲们
if they had any questions for me,
如果他们对我有任何疑问，
and here are some of the top questions that were sent
这是一些最重要的问题
in by you, the actual viewers.
实际观众是您的。
So first question is from Micho, who asks,
所以第一个问题来自米乔，他问，
how do I make the app-drawer panel automatically
我如何自动使应用程序抽屉面板
close when I click a link in my application?
当我单击应用程序中的链接时关闭？
So that's a really good question.
所以这是一个很好的问题。
I think we actually maybe used to do this
我认为我们实际上可能曾经这样做过
for you using the old Polymer Starter Kit,
为您使用旧的聚合物入门套件，
and we're not doing it now in the new Polymer Starter Kit.
并且我们现在不在新的Polymer Starter Kit中进行此操作。
But basically what you can do is you can actually wire up
但基本上您可以做的是实际上可以连线
a binding to the opened property,
与打开的属性的绑定，
or the opened attribute of the drawer panel,
或抽屉面板的open属性，
and then you can just toggle that value every time
然后您可以每次切换该值
the router changes the page.
路由器更改页面。
So that might not make sense when I'm just saying it
所以当我只是说出来时这可能没有意义
like this, and what I'll do instead
这样，我该怎么做
is I'll drop a link down in the description that
我将在说明中删除一个链接
has an example so you can just follow that.
有一个例子，所以你可以按照它。
And also, I think we might just add this behavior
而且，我想我们可能会添加这种行为
to the Polymer Starter Kit, the one that we just rolled.
到我们刚推出的聚合物入门工具包。
Maybe expected like a point release
也许像点发布一样
soon, when we just add this in you don't have to wire it up
很快，当我们将其添加到您中时，您无需将其连接起来
yourself.
你自己
So thank you for that question, Micho.
因此，谢谢您提出这个问题，Micho。
All right, this question comes from Eric Bidelman, who asks,
好的，这个问题来自埃里克·比德尔曼（Eric Bidelman），他问，
I hear Polymer 2's out.
我听到Polymer 2没电了。
What's up with that?
那是怎么回事？
So yeah, maybe some of you have seen
是的，也许你们当中有些人已经看到了
on Twitter and on the Polymer blog,
在Twitter和Polymer博客上，
we're recently tweeting that we have
我们最近在推特上说我们有
a preview branch of Polymer 2.0 available right now.
Polymer 2.0的预览分支现在可用。
You can find that over on the gitHubs,
您可以在gitHub上找到它，
and I will include a link to that, as well,
我还将包括一个链接，
down in the show notes.
在演出笔记中。
So Polymer 2, the main idea there is we
因此，聚合物2的主要思想是
want to get folks onto the new V1 versions of the web
希望将人们吸引到新的网络V1版本上
component standards.
组件标准。
So Custom Elements V1, and Shadow DOM v1.
因此，Custom Elements V1和Shadow DOM v1。
The current version of Polymer, 1.x,
当前版本的Polymer，1.x，
is based on the old V0 implementations.
基于旧的V0实现。
Those shipped in Chrome, and Opera, and some other browsers
Chrome，Opera和其他一些浏览器附带的软件
experimented with those versions of the standards,
试用了这些版本的标准，
but they are never going to be the native one
但他们永远不会成为本地人
that ships everywhere.
随处可见。
Instead, after reworking things a bit,
相反，经过一些修改，
the browsers decided to make some changes,
浏览器决定进行一些更改，
and those changes are in the V1 specs.
这些更改均在V1规范中进行。
So that's what's going to be shipping
这就是要运送的东西
in all the different browsers.
在所有不同的浏览器中。
I believe Safari recently just shipped Shadow DOM V1,
我相信Safari最近刚刚发布了Shadow DOM V1，
it'll be coming in Chrome really soon.
它将很快在Chrome中推出。
And because there are some breaking changes,
而且由于发生了一些重大变化，
we needed to migrate Polymer as well.
我们也需要迁移Polymer。
And the important thing to note here
这里要注意的重要事项
is that those breaking changes for the web component specs,
是Web组件规格的重大更改，
those are probably set in stone now.
这些可能现在已经定格了。
So we don't have to worry about suddenly a V2 appearing out
因此我们不必担心V2突然出现
of nowhere for the web component specs, or anything like that.
Web组件规格之类的东西无处不在。
The nice thing is that going forward,
好事是，向前迈进，
web component should be backwards compatible.
Web组件应向后兼容。
So yes, there are some breaking changes right now,
是的，现在有一些重大变化，
but hopefully minimal pain.
但希望疼痛最小。
I wrote down a few things from Polymer 2
我写下了Polymer 2的一些内容
that I'm really excited about, that I
我真的很兴奋，
wanted to tell you all about.
想告诉你所有。
Stuff that I just think is super cool.
我只是认为超棒的东西。
Aside from moving over to the new standards,
除了过渡到新标准之外，
we're going to be providing like a backwards compatibility
我们将提供向后兼容
layer.
层。
So if you've got a bunch of Polymer 1 elements,
因此，如果您有一堆Polymer 1元素，
and you want to try and start to migrate those to Polymer 2,
并且您想尝试将其迁移到Polymer 2
we have the old Polymer constructor available to you.
我们为您提供了旧的Polymer构造函数。
So you can seriously just do like a few small changes,
因此，您可以认真地做一些小的更改，
and voila, you've got Polymer 2 elements.
瞧，您已经有了Polymer 2元素。
But the other thing that we're doing now
但是我们现在正在做的另一件事
is we're baking in support for ES6 classes.
我们正在努力支持ES6类。
So that's something a lot of people really wanted.
所以这是很多人真正想要的。
Now, the default and the standard
现在，默认和标准
encouraged way to build a Polymer 2
鼓励的方式来制造聚合物2
element is going to be to actually inherit from a class.
元素将实际上是从类继承的。
And then you've got all the niceties
然后，您就拥有了所有的美感
of working with ES6 there.
在这里使用ES6。
We're getting rid of things like Polymer.DOM,
我们正在摆脱Polymer.DOM之类的东西，
which was always really confusing for folks,
这总是让人们感到困惑，
the whole shady DOM thing.
整个可疑的DOM事物。
Instead, we're going to be shipping a new, improved Shadow
取而代之的是，我们将发布新的，改进的Shadow
DOM polyfill.
DOM polyfill。
We're going to stop talking about local DOM, and shady DOM.
我们将不再谈论本地DOM和可疑DOM。
all these random terms that never made sense.
所有这些毫无意义的随机术语。
Instead we're just going to say, hey, it's Shadow DOM,
相反，我们只是说，嘿，这是Shadow DOM，
we got a new polyfill, it's nice and fast.
我们有一个新的polyfill，既好又快。
And we're making the data binding system a lot easier
而且我们使数据绑定系统更加容易
to reason about, too.
也要推理。
So if you ever had issues where you would change an object
因此，如果您遇到了要更改对象的问题
inside of an array, or change an object's sub-property
在数组内部，或更改对象的子属性
and things just wouldn't update, we
而且事情不会更新，我们
should be fixing those in Polymer 2
应该修复聚合物2中的那些
to make that just a lot more straightforward.
使这一点更加直接。
So that is kind of a high level overview.
因此，这是一个高级概述。
Again, I'll include a link for the 2.0 preview branch
同样，我将包含2.0预览分支的链接
down in the show notes.
在演出笔记中。
So you can go check it out yourself,
因此，您可以自己检查一下，
read through the readme, and give it a test run.
阅读自述文件，然后进行测试。
I'm really interested to hear what all of you think,
我真的很想听听大家的想法，
so please leave some comments down below
所以请在下面留下一些评论
with your thoughts on that.
您对此有何想法。
So thank you Eric for that question.
因此，谢谢您埃里克的问题。
Right, next question.
对，下一个问题。
Sam Saccone asks, I hear you are a corgi, what is up with that?
Sam Saccone问，我听说您是柯基犬，这是怎么回事？
So yeah, that's true.
是的，是的。
My spirit animal actually is the corgi.
我的精神动物实际上是小狗。
Thank you for that question, Sam.
谢谢你提出这个问题，山姆。
All right, our next question comes
好吧，我们的下一个问题来了
from Jerry, who asks, how do I implement
杰里问，我该如何实施
ES6 syntax with Polymer CLI?
使用Polymer CLI的ES6语法？
So today what you can do is you can use the custom build
所以今天您可以做的是使用自定义版本
generator that we showed off, I think, maybe two episodes ago.
我想，也许是两集之前我们展示过的发电机。
I'll include a link down in the show notes
我将在演出笔记中包含一个链接
to that particular episode.
该特定情节。
And what that does is it actually
那实际上是什么
gives you a little escape hatch out of the Polymer CLI build.
为您提供了Polymer CLI构建中的一些逃生功能。
It lets you actually use the same node
它允许您实际使用同一节点
module that powers the Polymer build,
为Polymer构建提供动力的模块，
but it lets you also hook into its lifecycle
但它也可以让您了解其生命周期
and add your own gulp tasks.
并添加您自己的任务。
One of those gulp tasks could be something like babel.
大量的任务之一可能是像babel这样的事情。
So you could write all your elements using HTML imports.
因此，您可以使用HTML导入来编写所有元素。
The Polymer build will actually split out the JavaScript
Polymer版本实际上将拆分JavaScript
into its own stream.
进入自己的流。
You then pass that through babel,
然后，您将其通过通天塔，
and then it recombines it all at the end for you.
然后在最后为您重新组合。
So that's the option that you could use today.
这就是您今天可以使用的选项。
However, as I mentioned before, we're
但是，正如我之前提到的，
going to be rolling out full blown ES6 support in Polymer 2.
即将在Polymer 2中推出完整的ES6支持。
So if you're able to wait to Polymer 2 time,
因此，如果您能够等待Polymer 2时间，
we might have a better story for you there.
我们可能在那里有个更好的故事。
It might be a little bit easier to use.
它可能会更容易使用。
So if I was doing this today, I would actually probably stick
因此，如果我今天这样做，我实际上可能会坚持
with just the current Polymer 1 syntax, and then wholesale move
仅使用当前的Polymer 1语法，然后批量移动
over to ES6 when Polymer 2 rolls out.
当聚合物2推出时，转到ES6。
Hope that answers your question.
希望这能回答你的问题。
Thank you, Jerry.
谢谢杰里。
All right the next question is from Stephen who says,
好吧，下一个问题来自斯蒂芬，他说：
I'm still confused about how to load in third party
我仍然对如何在第三方中加载感到困惑
JavaScript in my elements.
我的元素中有JavaScript。
So that's a question.
所以这是一个问题。
What a lot of people do, I've seen two approaches.
很多人在做什么，我已经看到了两种方法。
One approach would be, you just say, hey,
您可以说一种方法是，嘿，
I depend on this library, and you've
我依靠这个图书馆，而你已经
got to include the script tag for that library
必须包含该库的脚本标签
before you import your elements.
在导入元素之前。
What I actually prefer to do is to take the script
我实际上更喜欢做的是脚本
tag for whatever dependency I'm depending on,
标记我所依赖的任何依赖项，
put that into its own HTML import,
将其放入自己的HTML导入中，
and then have my elements import that file.
然后让我的元素导入该文件。
The nice thing there is your elements
好东西是你的元素
are now explicit about their dependency,
现在明确了他们的依赖性，
because that link tag is up at the top of their definition
因为该链接标记位于其定义的顶部
file.
文件。
And also, HTML imports will de-duplicate multiple requests
而且，HTML导入将删除多个请求的重复数据
to the same resource.
到相同的资源。
So if you've got five elements that are all
因此，如果您拥有五个要素
trying to import the same thing, it's
试图导入同一件事，这是
actually going to only be loaded one time.
实际上只会被加载一次。
So that's the approach that I really recommend using,
这就是我真正建议使用的方法，
that's the one that we've used in some of our elements,
那就是我们在某些元素中使用的那个
like the marked element.
就像标记的元素一样。
So yeah, hopefully that approach works for you.
是的，希望这种方法对您有用。
And also, I think in the future we're probably
而且，我认为将来我们可能
going to also be exploring things
也将探索事物
like maybe how we can use ES module loaders,
就像我们如何使用ES模块加载器一样
or something like that.
或类似的东西。
That's definitely in the Polymer 2 realm of possibilities.
这绝对是在Polymer 2领域的可能性。
So we might have an improved story there as well soon.
因此，我们可能很快也会有一个改进的故事。
So.
所以。
yeah, thank you Stephen for that question.
是的，谢谢斯蒂芬的问题。
All right, next question comes from Thomas
好吧，下一个问题来自托马斯
who asked, once all web component features are broadly
谁问过，一旦所有Web组件功能广泛
and correctly supported in all major browsers,
并在所有主流浏览器中得到正确的支持，
is Polymer's job done?
Polymer的工作完成了吗？
So yes and no a little bit.
是的，一点也不。
Definitely the job of polyfilling web components
绝对是填充Web组件的工作
is done at that point, which is great.
在这一点上完成了，这很棒。
We want to get rid of polyfills, we
我们想摆脱polyfills，我们
want to get rid of any sort of inconsistencies
想要摆脱任何类型的矛盾
that they introduce and just be doing everything native.
他们介绍了这些内容，并且正在做所有本地工作。
But web component standards are inherently low level,
但是Web组件标准本质上是低水平的，
and that's by design.
那是设计使然。
They're supposed to give developers maximum flexibility.
它们应该为开发人员提供最大的灵活性。
However, that also means that it can require a fair bit of code
但是，这也意味着它可能需要一些代码
to create your own elements, stamp out your Shadow DOM,
创建自己的元素，标记出Shadow DOM，
put your templates inside of them, and stuff like that.
将您的模板放入其中，诸如此类。
So Polymer will probably always be around in some fashion
因此，Polymer可能总是会以某种方式出现
to offer this sort of helper support, right?
提供这种帮助者支持，对吗？
Sometimes we refer to it as like sugaring the native web
有时我们称其为糖化本机网络
component standards.
组件标准。
Just making you essentially much more efficient.
只是使您实质上更有效率。
So that has kind of always been the direction for the library.
因此，这一直是图书馆的发展方向。
We wanted those polyfills to sort of evaporate away,
我们希望这些填料可以蒸发掉，
and then you're just left with this really nice clean helper
然后就剩下了这个非常好的清洁助手
library that just makes you more efficient as you're
库，使您在工作时更加高效
building components.
建筑构件。
So thank you, Thomas, for that question.
谢谢托马斯，这个问题。
All right, our next question comes
好吧，我们的下一个问题来了
from a user on Twitter named GBX,
来自Twitter上名为GBX的用户，
who says, how should web components be
谁说，网络组件应该如何
written to let applications override their default locales?
编写以使应用程序覆盖其默认语言环境？
So I am not personally an expert on localization
所以我个人不是本地化专家
or internationalization, I can't even say it.
或国际化，我什至不能说。
L10n, i18n.
L10n，i18n。
There we go, that's the easier way to go about it.
我们走了，那是解决这个问题的更简单方法。
My teammate, Monica Dinculescu has actually
我的队友Monica Dinculescu实际上
written some behaviors to help with these.
编写一些行为来帮助这些行为。
So the one that you would be interested in
所以你会感兴趣的那个
is called the app localized behavior.
称为应用程序本地化行为。
And basically, you define JSON file
基本上，您定义JSON文件
full of different localized strings based on the locale,
充满了根据语言环境的不同本地化字符串，
or that are keyed off of the locale.
或在语言环境之外输入的内容。
And then based on the user's locale,
然后根据用户的语言环境，
it then, in your element, it uses a little computer
然后，在您的元素中，它使用一台小型计算机
binding to match up whatever text
绑定以匹配任何文本
you're using to that JSON file and use the right localized
您正在使用该JSON文件并使用正确的本地化版本
version.
版。
So our internationalization library
所以我们的国际化图书馆
works in a very similar fashion.
以非常相似的方式工作。
The one thing to note is that these
要注意的一件事是，这些
depend on the internationalization API.
取决于国际化API。
And so if you're in a browser that does not support that API,
因此，如果您使用的浏览器不支持该API，
you're also going to need to include a little polyfill.
您还需要添加一些polyfill。
But that is linked to from the repo for app localize
但这是从回购链接到应用程序本地化的
and the i18n behaviors.
和i18n行为。
I'll include a link to these down in the show notes
我将在展示笔记中包含指向这些链接的链接
so you don't have to listen to me try and say
所以你不必听我说
these words anymore.
这些话了。
But yeah, give those a shot, and see if that helps in your app.
但是，是的，给那些机会，看看是否对您的应用有所帮助。
So thank you for that question, GBX.
因此，感谢您提出这个问题，GBX。
All right, next question is from Vladislav, who says,
好吧，下一个问题来自弗拉迪斯拉夫，他说，
what's up with 2.0-- Polymer 2.0,
2.0发生了什么-聚合物2.0，
I'm assuming-- and TypeScript?
我假设-和TypeScript？
So there's no plans right now to migrate over to TypeScript
因此，目前没有计划迁移到TypeScript
or anything like that.
或类似的东西。
However, we do have a lot of members of the Polymer team
但是，我们确实有许多Polymer小组成员
who really, really like TypeScript,
谁真的很喜欢TypeScript，
and we definitely want to make sure
我们肯定要确保
that we are supporting it better.
我们会更好地支持它。
So I think if you're trying to do this today,
所以我想，如果您今天尝试这样做，
you can maybe use something like the generator custom build
您也许可以使用类似生成器自定义版本的工具
that I mentioned before-- which we're
我之前提到的-我们
going to link to down the show notes-- to add the TypeScript
将链接到显示注释下-添加TypeScript
compile step to your gulp build process,
编译到您的gulp构建过程，
or something like that.
或类似的东西。
For 2.0 I'm not quite sure what the exact game
对于2.0，我不太确定确切的游戏是什么
plan is going to be, except for I'm almost certain that we're
计划将会是，除了我几乎可以确定我们
going to have some better TypeScript story,
会有更好的TypeScript故事，
some sort of improved story around it.
围绕它的某种改进的故事。
Because we have so many team members who like it,
因为我们有很多喜欢它的团队成员，
we have so many Googlers who like using TypeScript.
我们有很多喜欢使用TypeScript的Google员工。
I definitely want to explore it more myself, so I definitely
我绝对想亲自探索一下，所以我绝对
we'll probably have some more to talk about there.
我们可能还会在那儿谈论更多。
It's a little early days right now
现在还有些早
for Polymer 2.0 to know exactly what the strategy is
让Polymer 2.0确切了解该策略是什么
going to be.
将。
But if you're interested in TypeScript
但是，如果您对TypeScript感兴趣
and you're interested in Polymer,
您对Polymer感兴趣，
stay tuned, because I'm sure we're
请继续关注，因为我确定我们
going to have something more exciting for you
将会为您带来更多激动人心的东西
in the future on that topic.
将来在该主题上。
So thank you Vladislav for sending that in.
因此，感谢弗拉迪斯拉夫发送来的。
The last question comes from Ido,
最后一个问题来自伊藤
who says, how do I share information
谁说，我如何分享信息
when I am transitioning between two pages,
当我在两页之间切换时，
and what are the best practices for communicating
以及进行交流的最佳实践是什么
between elements?
元素之间？
So I'm actually going to answer this sort of in reverse order,
所以我实际上将以相反的顺序回答
because I think the second answer helps
因为我认为第二个答案有帮助
answer the first question.
回答第一个问题。
When you're communicating between elements,
当您在元素之间进行交流时，
you actually probably don't want to have
您实际上可能不想拥有
siblings talking to each other, or anything like that.
兄弟姐妹互相交谈或类似的话。
We generally try to discourage that,
我们通常会阻止这种情况，
mainly because it means that element A has
主要是因为这意味着元素A具有
to be coupled and know about element B over here.
耦合并了解元素B。
And we kind of don't want that level of coupling.
我们有点不希望这种耦合。
Instead, what we recommend is to figure out
相反，我们建议找出
a common parent between both of your elements
这两个元素之间的共同父母
and have your elements be kind of like as simple and as dumb
让您的元素变得既简单又愚蠢
as they can be and just dispatch events out
尽可能地将事件分发出去
to that common parent.
给那个共同的父母。
Like, hey, I was clicked on, or something like that.
就像，嘿，我被点击了，或类似的东西。
And then the common parent can act as the orchestrator,
然后，共同的父母可以充当协调者，
saying, oh, I hear that this child over here was clicked on,
说，哦，我听说这里的那个孩子被点击了，
and I know that that means that some action needs to happen
我知道那意味着需要采取一些行动
with child B over here.
和孩子B在这里。
What this does is that keeps element A and element
这是为了保留元素A和元素
B very simple, and re-usable.
B非常简单，并且可重复使用。
And all your business logic then kind of gets
然后您所有的业务逻辑都会得到
moved up into that higher order element.
向上移动到那个更高阶的元素。
And we usually refer to this as like a mediator component,
我们通常将其称为中介组件，
and I'll include a link down in the bottom to my teammate
我将在底部提供一个指向队友的链接
Kevin Schaaf's talk.
凯文·沙夫的讲话。
I think this is from Polymer Summit
我认为这是来自Polymer Summit
maybe two years ago, or a year ago,
大概是两年前或一年前，
where he talked about this pattern
他谈到这种模式的地方
and how we tend to use it in most of our apps.
以及我们倾向于在大多数应用中使用它的方式。
So that's how we recommend doing communication around the page.
因此，我们建议您在页面上进行交流。
And so then the first question was,
因此，第一个问题是，
how do I share information when I'm going from page 1
从第1页开始时如何共享信息
to page 2?
到第2页？
Well, in that case, I think if you have information
好吧，在那种情况下，我想如果您有信息
that needs to belong to multiple pages, that,
需要属于多个页面，
to me, is stuff that belongs in one of those higher order
对我来说，属于较高等级之一的东西
components.
组件。
Like something that kind of lords over all of the pages,
就像所有页面上的主人一样，
even.
甚至。
And it's just binding it down into the child pages.
它只是将其绑定到子页面中。
And you can have that higher level component
您可以拥有更高层次的组件
listen for changes coming out of some of these lower level
聆听一些较低级别的变化
components, and changing its state,
组件，并更改其状态，
and then pushing that down.
然后将其向下推。
But that way, again, you're simplifying things
但是那样又可以简化事情
so that the business logic where you've got two related
这样您就有两个相关的业务逻辑
things, the business logic for that
事物，为此的业务逻辑
is going to live higher up, and they
会活得更高，他们
don't have to try and talk to each other
不必尝试互相交谈
and figure out how each other works.
并找出彼此的工作方式。
So yeah, I hope that answers the question.
是的，我希望可以回答这个问题。
I know it's sort of like a broad, abstract answer,
我知道这有点像一个广泛的抽象答案，
but that's generally the pattern that we recommend.
但这通常是我们推荐的模式。
And definitely check out Kevin's talk,
一定要看看凯文的演讲，
which covers it in a lot more detail.
涵盖了更多细节。
So thank you Ido for that great question.
所以，谢谢Ido提出的这个好问题。
That about covers it for today.
大约涵盖了今天。
If you yourself have some questions for me,
如果您自己对我有疑问，
you can leave them down below in the comments,
您可以在下面的评论中将其保留下来，
or you can ping me on a social network of your choosing
或者您可以在您选择的社交网络上ping我
#AskPolymer.
#AskPolymer。
As always, thank you so much for watching,
和往常一样，非常感谢您的收看，
and I'll see you next time.
下次再见。
OK, ready?
准备好了？
Localization.
本土化。
Internationalization.
国际化。
I just slam it all together, so like, internationalizlation.
我只是一起抨击，就像国际化一样。
It's close enough.
足够近了。
That's why you just shorten it.
这就是为什么您要缩短它的原因。
You write i18n.
您写的是i18n。